

CONTACT

706-512-5489

Atlanta, GA

celiardiller@gmail.com

in <u>LinkedIn</u>

<u>Portfolio</u>

EDUCATION

Certificate in UI Design-Specialization in Frontend Development for Designers

Career Foundry

March 2021 – December 2021

BS in Biology and Business

St. Lawrence University

August 2016 – May 2020

SKILLS

- Adobe XD
- Atom
- Procreate
- Github
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Figma
- Marvel

CELIA DILLER

UI DESIGNER

SUMMARY

UX/UI Designer with a background in Biology and Business. Enjoys solving design problems and utilizing research findings to develop applications that are user-friendly. Experienced in building low, mid, and high-fidelity wireframes with user testing and research.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Social Media Marketing Intern and Fundraising Consultant

The Desoto Theatre

Rome, GA

September 2020 - December 2021

- Drove over \$25,000 of donations and funding by creating digital content (Instagram posts/stories, Facebook posts, videos, and slideshows).
- Increased website traffic and boosted ticket sales by 75% with social media marketing strategies.
- Expanded client communities by creating over a dozen digital presentations on social media marketing strategies which were presented to Board members to be used to help future showings.
- Efficiently drove donor engagements and revenue by helping board members develop an organizational system to preserve important historical documents and records.

UI Designer and Business Developmental Intern

Sunflour Bakery

Rome, GA

June 2019 - February 2022

- Led a two-month-long project as a UI Designer to design, photograph, and code Sunflour Bakery's homepage and online ordering system on their website. Responsible for user testing, establishing brand direction, and visual components to increase marketing and sales for the company.
- Created a social media analysis in the community to help assess the impact of current marketing strategies and improve future marketing campaigns.
- Constructed user testing on social media marketing strategies through the community and created a deep analysis of results to better create products for users.
- Increased sales by creating digital content that introduce new products and drove in new clientele.
- Maintained production of online orders, adding/editing inventory, adding new employees, and editing rewards systems by mastering the point-of-sale system (Clover).
 Resulted in a great customer satisfaction rate.

Sales Associate and Barista

Brewer Bookstore

Canton, NY

August 2016 - March 2020

- Developed and implemented new training programs for new student workers in the café.
- Created new coffee drinks and helped promote them through Instagram to the student body and faculty.
- Increased organization and implemented new protocols for café standards around the café for the bookstore team to use when teaching new hires.
- Provided knowledge of inventory and recommendations to customers in café and retail.

SPECIALTIES

- Wire-framing- Low, Medium and High Fidelity
 - a ringiririaciney
- Social Media Marketing
- User Interviews, Testing and Personas
- User Personas, Stories and Flows
- Coding in HTML, Java-Script, and CSS
- Typography and Iconography

Creating Brand Identities

Mockups and Prototypes